Guide to the Betty C. Jukes Papers
University of Houston Libraries
- Scrapbooks, Ephemera, and News Clippings, id163713
  - News Clippings, id163894
    - “Jr. Women’s Club Honors Guests”, Westside News, April 1969; id164354 (Ovsbox 26, Item 44)
    - “Be right: Uses for calling cards”, Houston Chronicle, December 1978; id164355 (Ovsbox 26, Item 45)
    - “Tanglewoodite elected president of Junior Woman’s Club”, Westside News, May 1972; id164356 (Ovsbox 26, Item 46)
    - “Talented Husband Is a Real Treasure”, Houston Chronicle, April 1969; id164357 (Ovsbox 26, Item 47)
    - “Tender Loving Care”, Westside News, April 1969; id164358 (Ovsbox 26, Item 48)
    - “The C-J Salutes”, Columbus Citizen-Journal, April 1973; id164359 (Ovsbox 26, Item 49)
    - “Gadabout”, Houston Chronicle, July 1974; id164360 (Ovsbox 26, Item 50)
    - “A Texas-Size Thank You to England’s Great Salesman: HRH Prince Philip”, Houston Chronicle, March 1966; id164361 (Ovsbox 26, Item 51)
    - “Goodwill Begets Goodwill”, Houston Post, March 1966; id164362 (Ovsbox 26, Item 52)
    - “Hope, Gaitlin lean toward topping Gavrel bill: Richard Tallboys, left, Winnie Carter, Russell Train”, Houston Post, October 1982; id164363 (Ovsbox 26, Item 53)
    - “Prince Philip sets casual tone”, Houston Chronicle, November 1982; id164364 (Ovsbox 26, Item 54)
    - “Man who spent 35 years carving Crazy Horse dies”, Houston Post, October 1982; id164365 (Ovsbox 26, Item 55)
    - “At home: Harris & Carroll Masterson”, Houston Post, October 1983; id164366 (Ovsbox 26, Item 56)
    - “What people are doing”, Houston Post, October 1983; id164367 (Ovsbox 26, Item 57)
    - “SUPER TEXANS…”, Houston Post, October 1983; id164368 (Ovsbox 26, Item 58)
    - “DeBakey keeps whirlwind pace as he nears 75”, Houston Post, September 1983; id164369 (Ovsbox 26, Item 59)
    - “LINDBERGH”, News and Record, March 2000; id164370 (Ovsbox 26, Item 60)
    - “He Talked, Money Walked”, Charlotte Observer, October 2009; id164371 (Ovsbox 26, Item 61)
    - “Living Mercury members to reunite here for banquet”, Houston Post, April 1984; id164372 (Ovsbox 26, Item 62)
    - “Friends of Girards pack Ma Maison for dinner”, Houston Post, April 1984; id164373 (Ovsbox 26, Item 63)
    - “Knox Bridges: THE MONEY TRAIL”, Charlotte Observer, October 2009; id164374 (Ovsbox 26, Item 64)
    - “Cruise to offer spectacular view of Halley”, Houston Post, December 1985; id164375 (Ovsbox 26, Item 65)
    - “State Department dinner shimmering milestone”, Houston Chronicle, December 1985; id164376 (Ovsbox 26, Item 66)
    - “Tents for stealing away Pakistani-style”, Houston Chronicle, July 1978; id164377 (Ovsbox 26, Item 67)
    - “Pearls of…”, Houston Post, July 1978; id164378 (Ovsbox 26, Item 68)
    - “‘Pearls of Pakistan’: Conceived as a gala exhibit of native crafts, it’s become a world marketing showcase”, Houston Post, July 1978; id164379 (Ovsbox 26, Item 69)
    - “Ben Shaw and style trends walked the same novel runways”, Houston Chronicle, July 1978; id164380 (Ovsbox 26, Item 70)